hennaforhair.com 2010-06-23

# Mehandi.com shop -

PRIVACY STATEMENT  
including hennapage.com, mehandi.com, hennaforhair.com and others owned by Catherine Cartwright-Jones  

Your privacy is important to TapDancing Lizard ®  LLC.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that TapDancing Lizard ®  LLC collects, and the ways TapDancing Lizard ®  LLC may use that personal information.

Personal information collection

TapDancing Lizard ®  LLC may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:   

  * information about your use of this website
  * information that you provide for the purpose purchasing products from the website
  * information about transactions carried out over this website including purchases and inquiries
  * any other information that you send to TapDancing Lizard ® LLC

Using personal information

TapDancing Lizard ®   LLC may use your personal information to:   

  * send to you products that you purchase
  * send you statements and invoices
  * collect payments from you
  * communicate with you

When TapDancing Lizard ® LLC discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. 

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified above, TapDancing Lizard ® LLC may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings,  in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.  

Securing your data

TapDancing Lizard ® LLC will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

TapDancing Lizard ® LLC will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. 

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be  protected by encryption technology.  

TapDancing Lizard ® LLC may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.  This website contains links to other websites.  TapDancing Lizard ® LLC is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.Contact  

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or When TapDancing Lizard ®   LLC's treatment of your personal information, please contact us by email: [info@mehandi.com](mailto:info@mehandi.com) or by mail: TapDancing Lizard ®   LLC 4237 Klein Ave., Stow, Ohio, 44224.  

This privacy statement is based on a precedent created by employmentlawcontracts.co.uk and published by freenetlaw.com.
